export const questions = [
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `What does the price of the product, indicated on the site, include?`,
    answer: `<p>The mentioned price is for the product and taxes (delivery charges are not included).</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Can I make a purchase without a credit card?`,
    answer: ` <p>In the absence of a credit card, you can make purchases both through
    online chat or by calling the Contact Center, and through the Idram
    payment system.</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `How do I know if my order has been confirmed?`,
    answer: `<p>After paying for purchases with a credit card, you will see a
    purchase confirmation with all the details, in the "Orders" section
    of your personal page, a copy of which will also be sent to your
    email.</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Can I cancel my order?`,
    answer: `<p>Yes, you can cancel your order (see the section “Terms and
        Conditions” point: “Purchase, Cancellation and Return Policy”).</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Can I make changes to my order?`,
    answer: `<p>Whether you made your purchases online or by phone, changes are only
    made by phone. To make changes, call at the following short number:
    8022.</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Can I return purchases I have already made?`,
    answer: `<p>Yes, you can, but delivery charges will not be refunded (see the
        section “Terms and Conditions” point “Purchase, Cancellation and
        Return Policy”).</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `What is “Personal page”?`,
    answer: `<p>In order to make purchases on the site, it is desirable that each user has 
    his own personal page - a profile. This is optional. If you do not have a personal page,
    you can make purchases, but you cannot see detailed information about previous purchases
    or repeat the same order.</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Where can I find a list of my purchases?`,
    answer: `<p>You can see a list of your purchases in your personal page and in
    your email. Your profile will store the history of your previous
    purchases, which allows you to repeat any of your previous orders if
    you wish.</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `I enter my credit card details, when will the money be charged from my card?`,
    answer: `<p>The amount is charged from your credit card only if you give such an order to the
     payment system by clicking on the "pay" button. The process usually takes only a few seconds.</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `I have a "Tsiran" store’s accumulating card. Can I use it to shop online?`,
    answer: `<p>All users of “Tsiran” store’s accumulating card can use it when making online 
    purchases, accumulate points and use them, according to the same principle as for offline purchases.</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `Who can I contact if I have problems purchasing on the site?`,
    answer: `<p>If you have any problems during online purchase, call at this short number: 8022</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: `How long does it take to complete a purchase on the site?`,
    answer: `<p>After choosing a list of products, it will take 3 minutes, but in general it depends 
    on the volume of your purchases (most of the time will be spent on choosing products).</p>`,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: ` Does tsiran.am allow my opinion to be posted in the “Comments” section if it is negative?`,
    answer: `<p> Any of your comments, positive or negative, will be posted in the “Comments” section, unless
     they contain content that does not comply with our site's policies. Otherwise, we have the right not to publish it at all. You can leave 2 types of 
     comments on the site:</p>
     <ol>
        <li>About the product sold on the site.</li>
        <li>About our site and service quality.</li>
     <ol>
    `,
  },
  {
    id: Math.random(),
    question: ` I live abroad. Can I make purchases on your website for my relatives living in Armenia?`,
    answer: `<p>Yes, you can.</br></br>

    Before making purchases, indicate your preferred branch of Tsiran, from where the delivery will be from, and before payment enter the recipient's data: address, name, surname, phone number. In this case, payment is made from abroad, and purchases are delivered to the specified address in Armenia. For more details on payment policy, see the section: "Terms and Conditions", point: "Credit Cards".
    </br></br>
    If you have additional questions or problems occured, please call: 012 80 80 22. </p>`,
  },
];
